saintclassified.pk 2016-11-02

# Privacy Policy - SaintClassified.pk

## **SaintClassified.pk Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us, so SaintClassified.pk has created this Privacy Policy to explain how your information is protected, collected and used. This Privacy Policy applies to all SaintClassified.pk web sites, including our publicly accessible web sites located at SaintClassified.pk.com ("SaintClassified.pk"). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. By using SaintClassified.pk, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future. If there is a conflict between our Terms of Use governing your use of the sites and this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use control.

****Collection**** **.**  Information posted on SaintClassified.pk is obviously publicly available. Our servers are located in the United States and in the European Union. Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers in the United States and Europe. We collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information;

  * computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from SaintClassified.pk and ad data (all through cookies - you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site);

  * other information, including your IP address and standard web log information.

****Use.**** ** ** We use your personal information to:

  * provide our services

  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;

  * encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;

  * customize the user experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;

  * communicate marketing and promotional offers to you;

  * do other things for users as described when we collect the information.

****Disclosure**** **.**  We don't sell or rent users' personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with:

  * corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).

  * service providers who help with our business operations.

****Using Information from SaintClassified.pk**** **:** You may use personal information gathered from SaintClassified.pk only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.

****Access, Modification, and Deletion.**** **** You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. Contact customer support (email@saintclassified.pk) to review any personal information we store that is not available on SaintClassified.pk. There may be a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent offenders from coming back.

****Security.****  We use many tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. We can't however guarantee the continuous functionality and liability of these tools at all times.

****General.****  We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to privacy@saintclassified.pk 

**Third Parties** We use third-party service providers to process purchases you make and to monitor our users’ interests. In addition, the Website may occasionally contain links to Third-Party Sites. If you click on the links to Third-Party Websites, you leave the Website. We are not responsible for the content of these Third-Party Websites or for the security of your personal information when you use the Third Party Websites. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Sites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal information that you may be subject to. They may collect information such as your IP address, browser specification, or operating system. This Privacy Policy does not govern personal information provided to, stored on, or used by these third-party providers and Third-Party Sites. We recommend that when you enter a Third-Party Site, you review the Third Party Site’s privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to the Website and Third-Party Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. On the Website, Google, as a third-party vendor, uses Cookies to serve ads. Google’s use of the DoubleClick DART Cookie enables it to serve ads to the Website’s users based on their visit to the Websites and Third-Party Websites. For more information on the DART Cookie see: <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx>. You may opt out of the use of the DART Cookie by Google by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy at: [ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). By publishing an ad on the Website, you acknowledge and agree that the Content is public and accessible by any third party and that they may appear in search engine results (such as Yahoo!, MSN, Google, Altavista, and other search engines) and in the cache of those search engines, in feeds and Third-Party Websites pursuant to cobranding agreements, and that it is the sole responsibility of each of those search engines, Third-Party Websites or RSS web feed resources to update and/or to remove Content from their indexes and their cache. You agree and acknowledge that SaintClassified.pk is not be liable for the information published in search results or by any Third-Party Website that carries SaintClassified.pk postings.

* * *

_**PRIVACY POLICY TV.SAINTCLASSIFIED.PK**_

Modified on 2011 August 24th 

This document sets out tv.saintclassified.pk’s commitment to your privacy and to the protection of personal data (the "Data") collected and processed in connection with your use of the Website, under the terms and conditions set out in the  **General Terms of Use**.

We collect and subsequently process (i) the Data that you voluntarily provide on the  **registration form**  on the Website including your user ID, a valid email address, and your date of birth and (ii) your IP address (the address of your computer) by an automatic collecting process.

Please note that whether or not you are a registered user, the Website may implement or allow third-party companies to implement automatic tracking processes (cookie or web beacon), which you may block by changing your browser settings. The Data (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) collected through these automatic tracking processes are anonymous and are used in order to improve the Website’s quality (as for examples the improvement of your search results and of the advertising selection provided to you).

Data indicated on the Website as mandatory is required in order to use the Website’s features (video uploads, comments, etc). Data automatically collected by the Website allows us to compile statistics on web page visits. Because tv.saintclassified.pk is a Lithuanian company, the Data is collected and maintained in Lithuania 

With exception for your non-personally identifiable information as stated in section 2, your Data is not transmitted to third parties. However, tv.saintclassified.pk may release Data if the law requires it to do so or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and applicable laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant or to protect tv.saintclassified.pk’s rights and interests. It is tv.saintclassified.pk’s policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon receipt of a subpoena, and not produce your Data until approximately two weeks after receipt of the subpoena, so that you will have adequate opportunity to move to quash the subpoena in court.

tv.saintclassified.pk attaches great importance to the security of your Data, and takes all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

Data is stored on the premises of the Website host and is kept only as long as necessary for the purposes set out above. After that point, data is kept only for statistical purposes and shall not be used for any other reason.

Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to register with tv.saintclassified.pk. It is tv.saintclassified.pk's policy not to collect any information from anyone under the age of 13.

In any case, you affirm that you are over the age of 13, as the Website is not intended for children under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, do not use or access the tv.saintclassified.pk website at any time or in any manner.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13, and that child has somehow registered with tv.saintclassified.pk, please send an e-mail to **** sahnafara@gmail.com ****  for instructions on how to cancel your child's registration.  In the e-mail, please provide your full name and address, your child's full name and address, your relationship to the child, your daytime and evening telephone numbers, your email address and a signed statement that you are the child's parent or legal guardian. tv.saintclassified.pk will use this information only to verify that you are the child's parent or legal guardian and for no other purposes.

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by requesting to do so via the Personal Info section of your profile or by sending an email to sahnafara@gmail.com
